嘿 你们周末有空的话
Oh, hey, if you guys are free this weekend,
我工作赢了一个品酒会
I won a night of wine tasting from work.
听起来很有意思
That sounds fun. Mm-hmm.
为什么科学家都不像销售员一样能有免费物品呢?
How come scientists don't win free stuff like salespeople do?
因为我们不是为了物品才干这一行的
'Cause we're not in it for the stuff.
我们是为了粉丝
We're in it for the groupies.
就我个人而言
Personally,
我觉得外部奖励简直看轻人
I find the notion of external rewards demeaning.
我追求科学是为了体验发现本身的快乐
I pursue science for the intrinsic joy of discovery.
但你总说你想获得诺贝尔奖
But you always say that you want to win a Nobel Prize.
我还说不要在朋友们面前反驳我
I also say don't contradict me in front of my friends,
但这个你就记不住了
but that you don't remember.
好吧 如果你们想去告诉我
All right, well, let me know if you guys want to go.
我想去
I would love to.
我确实喜欢陈年的黑比诺酒的丰富
I do enjoy the complexity of an aged Pinot noir.
我确定这个和你的
I'm sure that would pair nicely
油炸鸡块会很搭
with your fried nuggets of chicken.
听起来是个美妙的夜晚 我们应该去
Well, it sounds like a nice night. We should go.
又喝酒?
Wine again?
不了 谢谢你
Yeah, no, thank you.
我喜欢传统形式的葡萄
I like my grapes the old-fashioned way:
在果汁盒里
in a juice box.
好吧 我要去的
Well, I'm going.
你不能阻止我在商场享受按摩
You couldn't stop me from getting a massage at the mall,
你现在也不能阻止我去
and you're not stopping me now.
我不该看着我的女朋友
I shouldn't have to see my girlfriend
在公共场合被其他男人摸
get groped in public by another man.
我也不该看着我的男朋友
And I shouldn't have to see my boyfriend
在商场坐在儿童火车上
riding on a train for children around the mall.
给宝宝坐的小火车?
The little choo-choo for toddlers?
你现在知道我为什么需要按摩了吧
And now you know why I needed the massage.
我们就不去了
Well, we're out.
Bernie不能喝酒因为她怀孕了
Bernie can't drink 'cause she's pregnant.
她怀孕因为我们做爱了
And she's pregnant because we had sex.
我们做爱因为...
And we had sex because...
你懂得
well, come on.
没关系 你应该去
It's okay. You should go.
你确定?
You sure?
当然
Of course.
是的 让她休息一下 你懂得
Yeah, give her a break from, “Well, come on.”
Bernadette 看来周六晚上只有你和我了
Well, Bernadette, looks like Saturday night, it's you and me.
我? 怎样? 为什么?
Me? How? Why?
很自然啊
Well, it makes perfect sense.
你是个准妈妈 你不能喝酒
Because you're an expectant mother, you can't drink alcohol.
我也不喜欢
I don't like too.
你不能吃寿司
You can't have sushi.
我也不喜欢
I don't like too.
你不能用热水浴缸
You can't go in hot tubs.
我觉得它是大桶的出汗人汤
I consider them vats of sweaty people soup.
Sheldon 我不知道
Gee, Sheldon, I don't know.
来嘛
Oh, come on.
过山车 咖啡因 溏心蛋
Roller coasters, caffeine, runny eggs,
我这辈子都在回避这些东西
I've been avoiding these things all my life.
现在因为你怀孕了 你必须回避
And now, because you're pregnant, you have to.
区别是她将生机带来这个世界
The difference is she's bringing life into the world,
你是去除生机
and you suck it out.
我想我们可以试一下
I guess we could give it a try.
亲爱的小姐 你听说过丰盛的聚会
Well, little lady, you've heard of party hearty,
准备好参加贫乏聚会
get ready to party hardly.
我赌你现在想喝一杯
I bet you'd like a drink right now.
* 宇宙一度又烫又稠密 *
* Our whole universe was in a hot, dense state *
* 140亿年前终于爆了炸... 等着瞧! *
* Then nearly 14 billion years ago expansion started... Wait! *
* 地球开始降温 *
* The Earth began to cool *
* 自养生物来起哄 穴居人发明工具 *
* The autotrophs began to drool, Neanderthals developed tools *
* 我们建长城 我们建金字塔 *
* We built the Wall * * We built the pyramids *
* 数学 自然科学 历史 揭开神秘 *
* Math, Science, History, unraveling the mystery *
* 一切由大爆炸开始 *
* That all started with a big bang *
生活大爆炸 第九季第22集
--==圣城家园SCG字幕组 http://hdscg.com/==--
仅供翻译交流使用, 禁止用于商业用途
协调: 酥酥final要爆炸
校对: UUUUUU
翻译: 舒大卷子 波特妹子 無限月讀
你觉得如果我
Hey, you think it'd be okay
带Claire去品酒会可以吗
if I brought Claire to the wine tasting?
- 当然 我想见见她  - 太好了
- Sure. I'd like to meet her.  - Oh, that's great.
我也一直想让她见见你们
I've been wanting her to meet you guys, too,
这次似乎是个好机会
so this seems like the perfect opportunity.
但我不在
Oh, but I won't be there.
真有意思怎么办呢
Funny how that worked out.
这意味着你和Emily分开了?
Does this mean Emily's not in the picture anymore?
没有 我还在和她约会
No, I'm still dating her.
给我解释一下
Okay, help me out.
你是怎么做的?
How are you doing this?
她们知道对方吗?
Do they know about each other?
她们知道我们不是专一的
They know that we're not exclusive,
还有我们不会问太多问题
and we just don't ask too many questions.
你知道 这就像我和你一起玩卡尔战神
You know, it's like how I play Warlords of Ka'a with you
和Frank和Alicia一起玩远古印记
and Elder Sign with Frank and Alicia.
Frank和Alicia是谁?
Who's Frank and Alicia?
你和我在一起的时间很长
Y... You and I spend a lot of time together.
就不能保持一点神秘感吗?
Can there be a little mystery between us?
好了
Okay.
所有装置已连接 我们准备好了
Everything's hooked up. We're ready.
我要给后人记录下这一刻
I am going to record this for posterity.
好 不会有什么希望
All right, here goes nothing.
不会有什么希望?
Here goes nothing?
这是我们构想的初始测试
This is the initial test of our prototype.
可以稍微庄严一点吗?
Can we give it a little more gravitas?
好吧
Fine.
永动陀螺回转导航系统
Preliminary trial of the infinite persistence
初步测试: 第一阶段开始
gyroscopic navigational system: phase one commencing.
问题可能出在你的嗓音
Eh... maybe it's your voice.
我要看看之后能不能请James Earl Jones来念
I'm gonna see if I can get James Earl Jones to do it in post.
哦
Ooh.
哇哦
Wow.
好美
It's... it's-it's beautiful.
实际上 它搞得我头晕
Actually, it's making me dizzy.
太好了 不仅仅是我
Good, it's not just me.
喂
Hello.
嘿 Claire
Hey, Claire.
嘿 怎么了?
Hey, what's up?
嘿 呃
Hi, yeah.
我在想
Um, I was wondering,
你周末有没有空
if you're free Saturday night,
我的朋友们都要去一个品酒会
all my friends are going to a wine tasting.
有空 我想
Sure, I guess.
如果你不觉得见你的朋友们对我们来说有点太快的话
If you don't think meeting your friends is too big a step.
为什么会太快?
Why would it be too big a step?
我不知道 我只是不想让事情变得奇怪
I don't know. I just don't want things to get weird.
没什么好担心的
Nothing to worry about.
人们无时无刻不在见面
People meet people all the time,
一点都不奇怪
and it isn't weird.
我曾经见到Bon Jovi 你觉得可能会奇怪的那个
I met Bon Jovi once, which you'd think might be weird.
结果 非常愉快
Turns out, total sweetheart.
好吧 但我们要顺其自然
Okay, but you and I have been keeping things casual.
你会介绍我是你的朋友
Uh, will you introduce me as your friend
还是女朋友
or as your girlfriend?
如果我喜欢他们
What if I like them
他们不喜欢我怎么办?
and they don't like me?
如果他们喜欢我而我不喜欢他们怎么办?
What if they like me and I don't like them?
和Bon Jovi见面那次可没这么困难
Boy, it wasn't this hard with Bon Jovi.
我说 "你很酷" 他说 "谢谢"
I said, “You rock,” he said, “Thanks, man,”
就完了
and that was that.
嘿 你准备走了吗?
Hey, you ready to go?
- 等下  - 你在干什么?
- Hang on.  - What are you doing?
找到一本擦嗅的关于品酒的书
Oh, I found a scratch-and-sniff book about wine tasting.
讲授寻找红酒的不同风味
It teaches the different flavor notes to look for.
你真的闻到酒味了?
You actually smell the wine?
基本上是我的鼻用喷雾的味道
I mostly just smell my nasal spray.
你的鼻炎又发作了?
Are your sinuses acting up?
自从我在幼儿园得到一只兔子
Since my preschool got a bunny.
你今晚还是和Bernadette一起玩吗?
Hey, are you still hanging out with Bernadette tonight?
是呀
Yes.
我们要证明我们不需要酒精
And we're going to prove that we don't need alcohol
就可以玩得很开心
to enjoy ourselves.
好样的
Oh, good for you.
或者咖啡因 烟草 寿司
Or caffeine, tobacco, sushi,
软奶酪 加工肉类和浴缸
soft cheese, processed meats and Jacuzzis,
这些对于胎儿来说都有害
which can all be harmful to an unborn baby.
没有在浴缸里的蜂蜜火腿 知道了
No HoneyBaked Ham in a hot tub-- got it.
也没有泡泡浴
Oh, no bubble baths either.
他们会增加尿路感染的危险
They can increase the risk of a urinary tract infection.
好的 玩的高兴
Okay, have fun.
还没有箭鱼 青花鱼 鲨鱼或者方头鱼
Oh, and no swordfish, king mackerel, shark or tilefish,
这些含汞量很高
which are all high in mercury.
我们走啦!
We're leaving now!
不能接触豚鼠
Oh, and no contact with guinea pigs
仓鼠或他们的排泄物
or hamsters or their droppings,
不能有猫砂盒 油漆味
uh, no-no cat litter boxes, no paint fumes...
我们走了 爱你 再见!
Okay, we're leaving, love you, bye!
天 我太爱约束了
Boy, do I love restrictions.
嘿
Hey.
大家人呢?
Where is everybody?
我们是先到的
Oh, we're the first ones here.
哦
Oh.
好吧
Cool.
嗯
Yeah.
好啊
Cool.
我都不记得上次我们单独
You know, I don't remember the last time
相处是什么时候了
it was just you and me hanging out.
我记得 三年前
Oh, I do. It was three years ago.
对哦 当时我们说要常玩的
Oh, yeah, and we said we should do it more often.
然后... 就到现在了
And... and here we are.
所以Sheldon和Bernadette在一起玩
So, Sheldon and Bernadette are hanging out.
是啊 他们会聊些什么呢?
I know. What are they gonna talk about?
我不知道
I don't know.
真的不知道呀
I really don't know.
嘿
Hey.
- 太好了!  - 谢天谢地!
- Oh, good!  - Oh, thank God!
你们来很久了吗?
You guys been here long?
没 就两分钟
No, two minutes.
但度秒如年
But yes.
Claire呢?
Where's Claire?
哦 她直接来这里跟我们见面
Oh, she's meeting us here.
各位 帮个忙别问太多关于
Hey, guys, do me a favor and don't ask too many questions
我们关系的问题
about the relationship.
我们在慢慢来
We're just keeping it casual.
所以我不应该问她作为你妻妾的一员
Oh, so I shouldn't ask her how she feels about being
有何感受咯?
a member of your harem?
我知道你在打趣 但小心遭报应
Yeah, I know you're teasing, but watch out for karma.
嘿 Penny 那不是你前男友Zack吗?
Hey, Penny, isn't that your old boyfriend Zack?
是哦
Oh, yeah.
你要跟他打招呼吗?
Are you gonna say hi to him?
不知道哎
Uh, I don't know.
在你做决定的空当
Hey, while you decide,
谁床上功夫更好呢:
who was better in bed:
大帅哥Zack还是小喘男Leonard?
big hot Zack or wheezy little Leonard?
哩哩啦啦
Neener neener.
我带了气泡苹果汁
I brought sparkling cider.
哦... 泡泡搞得我鼻子痒
Oh... the bubbles tickle my nose.
我还是现在就打开
I'll just open this now so it can get
这样喝的时候就没有气泡更爽口了
nice and flat before we drink it.
你今晚想干什么?
So what do you want to do tonight?
哦 我可是好好规划了一番呢
Oh, I have quite the evening planned.
我们的胎儿友好欢乐节始于
Our fetus-friendly festival of fun begins
对模型火车世界的
with an in-depth look
深入了解
at the world of model trains,
然后我们会加大欢乐力度
and then we'll kick things up a notch and explore
探索烤吐司的不同方式
all the different ways that you can make toast.
难道不止一种?
There's more than one?
- 你听过法国吐司吗?  - 嗯
- You've heard of French toast?  - Yeah.
- 肉桂吐司?  - 嗯
- Cinnamon toast?  - Yeah.
- 梅尔巴吐司?  - 嗯
- Melba toast?  - Yeah.
你明白我意思了吗?
You get where I'm going here?
嗯
Yeah.
我闻到了泥土的味道
I'm getting an earthy note.
绝对有橡树
Ah, there's definitely some oak.
还有 樱桃?
Also, uh, cherries?
我什么也没闻到
I smell nothing.
真的? 什么也没有?
Really? Nothing?
就... 很浓的阿氟林味儿
Just a... whole lot of Afrin.
Penny是你?
Penny?
你好 Zack!
Oh. Zack, hi!
你们都记得Zack吧
You guys remember Zack.
- 嗯 你好  - 你好  - 嘿
- Yeah, hey, buddy.  - Hello.  - Hey.
你们俩结婚了吗?
Hey, did you two get married?
- 是的  - 嗯
- We did.  - Yeah, mm-hmm.
和对方?
To each other?
对
Yes.
挺好 因为除了你跟他分手
Cool. 'Cause other than when you broke up with him
和我在一起 然后和我分手
and dated me, then broke up with me,
再和我在一起 然后跟他复合之外
and then dated me one more time before going back to him,
我都一直支持你们俩的
I was always rooting for you two.
谢谢
Thanks.
科研怎么样了?
So how's the science world?
你们研究什么呢?
What are you guys up to?
我们在为自己发明的导航系统
W-We've actually been working on a prototype
研发模型
for a navigation system we invented.
但我们就不拿细节烦你了
But we won't bore you with the details.
开玩笑吗? 我爱科学
Are you kidding? I love science.
爱因斯坦 斯蒂芬·霍金 迈克·德葛拉司·泰森(实为奈尔·德葛拉司·泰森 天文学家)
Einstein, Stephen Hawking, Mike deGrasse Tyson.
迈克·德葛拉司·泰森?
Mike deGrasse Tyson?
对啊 就是那个拳击手(拳王泰森)留了胡子
Yeah, you know, the boxer who grew a mustache
当起科学家了
and became a scientist.
你们的发明是什么?
So what's your invention?
我们要用量子漩涡
Well, we're using quantum vortices
来代替导航系统中的陀螺仪
to replace gyroscopes in guidance systems.
妙的是它们可以永久
What's neat is that they can maintain
维持角动量
angular momentum indefinitely.
角动量哈
Angular momentum.
我正想它呢
I was wondering about that.
你可以把它装在卫星或火箭上
You could put it in a satellite or a rocket,
它就会一直运行下去
and it'll run forever.
厉害啊
Cool.
它可以被用于导弹或战争中吗?
Could it be used for missiles and war stuff?
可以 但我们不是想造武器啊
Yeah, but we didn't create it for weapons.
而且我也怀疑军方会对我们的
And I doubt the military would be interested
小小导航系统感兴趣
in our little guidance system.
它比军方现在用的好吗?
Is it better than the one they use now?
- 好太多!  - 没得比
- A lot!  - Way better.
哈
Huh.
你确定你们聪明吗?
You sure you guys are smart?
"H-O"规格的火车是1:87的比例
"H-O" gauge trains are 1/87 scale.
"N"规格的是1:160的比例
"N" gauge are 1/160 scale.
然后就到了"Z"规格 它的是
And that brings us to "Z" gauge, at a
"你可以轻易吞到肚子里 别问我怎么知道的"规格 比例1:200
"you could easily swallow it, don't ask how I know," 1/220.
抱歉 我还是得问
I'm sorry, I have to ask.
我五岁的时候 吞下了一个"Z"规格的火车
When I was five, I ingested a "Z" gauge locomotive.
我接下来三天都在说 "我能拉出来
I spent the next three days saying, "I think I can pass it,
我能拉出来 我能拉出来"
I think I can pass it, I think I can pass it."
你为什么这么喜欢火车?
What is it about trains that you like so much?
这问题有意思
What an interesting question.
我小的时候 生活对我来说
When I was a child, life was confusing
困惑又混乱 而火车代表着秩序
and chaotic for me, and trains represented order.
我可以给它们排队 分类 控制它们
I could line them up, categorize them, control them.
我想你可以说
I guess you could say that
它们在纷扰的世界中给了我一丝平静
they gave me a sense of calm in a world that didn't.
说的太好了 Sheldon
That's lovely, Sheldon.
嗯... 除了一点点驶过你肚子的时候之外
Well... other than when they're chugging through your bowels,
这些东西充满魔力
these things are magic.
我必须承认 从我们开始讨论这个开始
I have to admit, I've been worried about
我一直在担心军方应用
the military applications since we started talking about this.
我也是
Me, too.
你怎么不说啊?
Why didn't you say something?
跟我不讨论肛门癌的原因一样
Same reason I don't talk about ass cancer.
这不是什么愉快的话题
It's not a pleasant topic.
你不能让这个阻止你们
You can't let this stop you.
几乎所有的科学发展都可以被用在
Almost any scientific advancement can be used
毁灭性的事情上
for destructive purposes.
没错 就连爱因斯坦的相对论
It's true. Even Einstein's theory of relativity
之后也被用在了核武器的研发上
was later applied to the development of nuclear weapons.
E等于MC的平方(爱因斯坦著名的相对论公式)
E equals MC squared.
是啊
Yeah.
"E"是能量 "M"是质量
"E" is for energy, "M" for mass,
而"C"是光速
and "C" for the speed of light.
你怎么知道的?
How do you know that?
Leonard想延长做爱时间的时候就嘟囔这些
Oh, Leonard mumbles it when he wants sex to last longer.
嘿 Raj
Hey, Raj.
嘿 Claire 你来了太好了
Hey, Claire. Good, you're here.
各位 这是我的朋友Claire
Guys, this is my friend Claire.
我们在非正式地交往 然后没有必要
We're casually dating, and there's no need
问任何问题了
for any further questions about it.
你想喝杯酒吗?
Would you like a glass of wine?
说了不许问问题!
I said no questions!
最后一个重要嘉宾
And last but not least,
我喜欢称之为星球大战吐司 因为...
this is one that I like to call Star Wars Toast because...
它有光明面和黑暗面
it has a light side and a dark side.
好了 地下城与勇士的时间到了!
All righty, it's time for Dungeons & Dragons!
地下城与勇士
Dungeons & Dragons.
听着很"好玩"啊
That sounds about right.
你会喜欢的
You're gonna enjoy this.
我专门为你设计的
I designed it especially for you.
好吧 但就玩一会儿
Okay, but just for a little bit.
哦 我预感你一旦开始了
Oh, I have a feeling that once you start,
你就不想停下 也不准停下
you're not gonna want to or be allowed to stop.
好吧
All right.
准备好了吗?
Ready?
当然了
You bet.
你叫作
Your name is
Bernatrix.
Bernatrix
你是战士女王
You are a warrior queen.
你又强又高又漂亮
You're strong, beautiful and tall.
我喜欢长得高
Oh. I like the idea of being tall.
我觉得有不少你喜欢的设定
I think you're gonna like a lot of things I have in store.
例如 在这个世界里 只有男人才会怀孕
For example, in this world, only the men get pregnant,
所以你老公在家里笑的时候要忍住不尿出来
so your husband is home trying not to pee when he laughs.
开始变得有趣了 接下来呢?
This is getting fun. What's next?
你又渴又倦的从战场归来
You're parched and weary from battle.
站在一个旅馆前 旅馆里有全国
You stand in front of a tavern that serves the coldest,
最冰凉最可口的麦芽酒
most delicious ale in all the realm.
我好几个月没喝酒了
Oh, I haven't had a drink in months.
你会干什么?
What do you do?
我飞速跑进去 把剑扔在地上
I storm in, slam my sword down,
然后说 小二 把店里最烈的麦芽酒
and say, “Barkeep, bring me the strongest ale you have
装在哥布林的头颅里给老娘端上来!
and serve it in the skull of a goblin!”
他要查你身份证
He wants to see I.D.
Claire 我们听说了不少关于你的有趣的事情
So, Claire, we've heard so many wonderful things about you.
真的? 比如呢?
Really? Like what?
呃 主要是Penny听说的
Uh, mostly Penny's heard them.
你去那边要求酒里加冰的时候
Boy, you get some dirty looks over there
得看不少脸色
when you ask for ice.
Zack 这是我朋友Claire
Zack, this is my friend Claire.
你条子真正 有男朋友了吗?
You're hot. You seeing anybody?
我就是她男朋友
Uh, she's seeing me.
那你为什么说她只是你朋友?
Why'd you say she's your friend?
我们只是想随便一点
We're just keeping it casual.
为什么他要跟你随便? 你很不错
Why is he being casual with you? You seem great.
我也不知道 问他
I don't know. Ask him.
为什么你要跟他随便? 她很不错
Why are you being casual with her? She seems great.
也许我们该后退一步
Maybe we should take a step back.
后退一步?
Take a step back?
我可不是年轻人了
I'm not a young man anymore.
不 我是说重新考量该拿导航系统怎么办
No, I mean reevaluate what we're doing with the guidance system.
可我要当爹了
But I got a baby on the way.
我得赚钱
I got to make some money.
如果我们不小心导致了世界末日
What good is money gonna do
那钱又有什么用?
if we inadvertently bring about Armageddon?
得了 我跟你讲
Okay, let me stop you right there.
我们绝对有把握
We absolutely know
我们的发明不会用来毁灭世界
our invention will not be used to destroy the world.
怎么说?
How?
因为没人从未来返回来
Because no one from the future
刺杀我们
has come back to kill us.
很有意思
Very funny.
还有更好的理由吗?
You got something better?
呃 没了
Well, not really.
好吧 那么
Okay, then.
天啊 你究竟喝了多少酒?
Geez, how much wine did you drink?
没多少 直到你走开我才尿得出来
Not a lot. I just couldn't start until you walked away.
地狱虾从温泉里冲出来!
The Hell Prawn lunges out of the hot spring!
你用盾格挡开
You block it with your shield.
你要反击吗?
Do you attack?
它有眼睛吗?
Does it have eyes?
三个血红的大眼睛都不眨一下
Three giant red ones and they never blink.
看着瘆人
It's unsettling.
我捅向中间的眼睛!
I stab it in the middle eye!
好办法!
Good choice!
暴击了! 你的剑
Critical hit! Your sword goes
刺穿它的眼睛插入脑子里
through its eye into its tiny brain.
它用最后一口气说
With its final dying gasp, it says,
你把我
You have reduced me
做成了一块寿司
“to a pile of sushi.
伴着酱油食用
“Enjoy me
风味更佳
“with this packet of soy sauce.
这是低钠酱油
It's low sodium.”
好吧 我想我要吃了地狱虾
Okay, I guess I should eat the Hell Prawn.
你用剑
Using your sword,
做成了好看的寿司大餐
you prepare a beautiful sushi dinner.
你跳进温泉 热水抚慰
You slip into the hot spring and enjoy the warm water
你酸痛的关节
on your aching joints.
你幸福的闭上眼
As you happily close your eyes,
想起那个愉快的晚上
you recall the incredible evening you've had
注意到
and notice that your...
你的脚和脚踝变得比以前都小了
feet and ankles are smaller than they've ever been.
全剧终
The end.
今晚比我预想的有意思多了
Wow, this night turned out to be so much more fun than I thought.
还没完呢
Oh, the fun doesn't stop.
你回家时还能带走一整袋烤面包
You're still going home with a goodie bag full of toast.
谢谢你
Thank you for this.
自从别人知道我怀孕了
You know, ever since people found out I'm having a baby,
他们都拿我当孕妇
I feel like I became Pregnant Bernadette.
今晚能休息一下很舒服
It was nice to take a little break tonight.
我能理解
I can understand that.
自从人们发现我是天才
From the moment people realized I was a genius,
我就成了天才Sheldon
I've been Sheldon the Genius.
但是我从没想要休息一下
Although I've never really wanted a break from that,
所以我也未必理解
so I suppose I don't understand.
可笑的是
Which is ironic
你知道 我是天才
'cause, you know, genius.
好了 再次谢谢你
Well, thanks again.
没事
You're welcome.
每当你想从孕妇Bernadette
And any time you need a break
跳脱出来休息一会
from being Bernadette the Pregnant,
随时都能变成战士女王Bernatrix
Bernatrix the Warrior Queen is here waiting.
我会记住你说的
I might just take you up on that.
你得记住
Well, mind you now,
妊娠三期之前才能来玩
that offer's only good until the third trimester.
我可受不了羊水洒在我的座位上
I can't risk getting amniotic fluid on my spot.
伙计 关于Claire你让我很为难
Hey, dude, you're killing me with Claire.
你说什么呢?
What are you talking about?
我是说 看看你
I mean, come on, look at you.
你又帅 又有游泳运动员的身材
You're classically handsome, you've got a swimmer's body.
在你旁边 我看起来很挫
Next to you, I look like me.
抱歉 我不是故意的
Oh, man, I didn't mean to do that.
但是你夸赞我游泳运动员的身材让我很爽
But I do appreciate you recognizing my swimmer's body.
随便说一句
Which, incidentally,
这是我在基督教青年会里玩马可波罗游戏时练出来的
I got from playing Marco Polo at the YMCA.
好了 帮帮忙
Yeah, okay, just... do me a favor
别再恭维Claire了
and stop talking about how great Claire is.
乐意效劳 我的外国小朋友
Anything for you, my little foreign friend.
我得问问
So, I got to ask,
Raj带其他女孩来了吗?
does Raj bring around other girls?
你知道
Uh, you know,
我知道的不多
I... I'm not really around that much.
Amy了解的比我清楚
Amy knows much more than I do.
我不觉得你有什么好担心的
I don't think you have anything to worry about.
Raj是个好小伙 对恋人忠诚
Raj is a terrific guy, loyal to a fault.
他还有美国在线地址
Yeah. He still has an AOL address.
我明白你说的
I see what you're saying.
她没那么好
She's not so great.
别听他的
Don't listen to him.
他总是胡说八道
He says crazy things all the time.
你看 马克
Uh, watch. Marco.
波罗!
Polo!
你们聊什么呢?
So, uh, what are you guys talking about?
你朋友在跟我讲
Your friends were just telling me about
你交往的其它女孩
all the other girls you're dating.
你们为什么要这么干?
Why would you do that?
我特意交代过别这样
I specifically asked you not to do that.
我们没有啊
We didn't.
你自己刚承认了
You just did.
哇 或许你们都不是聪明人
Wow. Maybe none of you guys are smart.
早
Morning.
喝太多酒了
Ugh. Too much wine.
我昨晚
Oh, I overdid it
也过头了
myself last night.
自食其果
Hair of the dog.
你有没有想过导航系统
Hey, did you ever think about the military applications
的军事运用?
for the guidance system?
当然有
Of course.
有困扰过你吗?
Does it bother you?
最开始有过
No, it did at first,
可是跟Frank和Alicia探讨过后...
but then I talked it through with Frank and Alicia, and...
他们帮助我看清事实真相
they really helped put things into perspective.
那些都是谁啊?
Who are these people?
Leonard 朋友就像厕纸
Leonard, friends are like toilet paper.
马桶后有备份总是好的
It's good to have extras under the sink.